It's very important to go on an inner journey
进行内在旅程是非常重要的，
but it's as possible to get lost on an inner journey
但是在内在旅程中迷失方向
as it is in an outward journey in the world.
和在世界的外部旅程中迷失方向有着同样的可能性。
So what we try to do in the courage to teach retreats
因此，我们在教学勇气静修中
is to create a form of community
尝试做的是创造一种社区形式，
in which people can go inward
在其中人们可以向内探索，
they can go inward through reflecting on poetry or
他们可以通过反思诗歌或
stories from some of the great spiritual traditions
来自一些伟大的灵性传统的故事向内探索，
that raise critical questions about our lives.
提出关于我们生命的关键问题。
They can go inward in silence,
他们可以在静默中向内探索，
they can go inward through journal,
他们可以通过写日记、
walks in the woods,
在树林中散步来向内探索，
all the simple ways that human beings have
所有这些简单的方式都是
of becoming more reflective of taking time
让人们变得更有反思性而有时间
to simply listen to their hearts,
只是去地倾听他们自己的心声，
to let the world get quiet
让世界安静下来，
and hear what they can hear from in here.
听听他们能从中听到什么。
But it's very important to come out of that solitude
但非常重要的是，要从这种独处中走出来，
into a community that's willing
进入一个愿意倾听你的想法、
to hear what you think, you have learned,
你所学到的东西的社区，
not to judge it,
而不是评判它，
not to tell you whether it's right or wrong,
不是告诉你它是对的还是错的，
but to hear it in a way that allows you
而是以一种让你能以更深入地
to hear yourself more deeply.
倾听自己的方式来倾听它。
One of the things that I always
我经常对静修小组
say to retreat groups is
说的一件事是，
that we have a strange conceit in western culture
在西方文化中我们有一种奇怪的自负，
which is that just because we've said something,
那就是仅仅因为我们说了什么，
we think we know what we've said.
我们就认为我们知道自己说了什么。
And the most important things we say
而我们说的最重要的事情，
especially under these reflective conditions are
尤其是在这些反思的条件下，
often things that come from what I call the inner teacher.
往往是来自我所说的内在老师的事情。
I don't alone call it that,
我并不单独这样称呼它，
I'm a quaker and in the quaker tradition
我是一个贵格会教徒，在贵格会传统中，
there's a 400 year history of affirming
我们有一个400年的历史，
that every human being has an inner teacher.
我们相信每个人都有一个内在老师。
When the inner teacher speaks through my mouth,
当内在老师通过我的嘴说话时，
it may take me years to understand what I've just said
我可能要花好几年的时间来理解我刚才说的话，
and what its implications are for my life.
以及它对我的生活有什么影响。
But that process is going to be greatly helped along
但这个过程会因为有
by having a community of people
一个愿意听我说话的社区
who are willing to hear me into speech,
而得到很大的帮助，
who are willing to let me say
他们愿意让我
whatever is truly on my heart and mind,
说出我心中真正的想法，
not to judge it, not to fix it,
而不是去评判它，不是去修正它，
not to advise me, not to set me straight,
不是去建议我，不是去纠正我，
but simply to let me hear myself at a deeper level.
而只是让我在更深的层次上听到自己。
And that's a very special form of community.
这是一种非常特殊的社区形式。
I think it's a community that most people
我认为这是一个大多数人
have hardly any experience with if at all.
几乎没有任何经验的社区。
Because it's a community that engages you
因为这是一个让你参与的社区，
but it doesn't engage you with fixes or saves,
但它不是用修正或拯救的方式让你参与，
it engages you with first of all listening
它首先让你全然倾听，
and then with honest open questions,
然后是提出诚实的开放性的问题，
what did you mean when you said that,
比如，"当你这么说的时候，你指的是什么？
can you say more about that,
你能多说一点吗?
is what you're talking about
你说的东西是不是以某种方式
connected in some way to other areas of your life.
与你生活的其他领域有关？"
This is the kind of community we try to create
这就是我们在静修小组中
in our retreat groups.
试图创建的社区。
And I think it's a kind of community that
而且我认为这是
teachers find astonishing in
一种教师发现对他们的生活
its positive consequences for their lives.
产生惊人的积极影响的社区。